<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ooo_calc_export scriptVersion="2.2.0_qdxml" scriptUpdate="2011-03-02" scriptURL="http://www.digitalimprint.com/misc/oooexport/" scriptAuthor="vjl">
  <ooo_sheet num="1">
    <ooo_row><column_1>loc_key</column_1><column_2>value</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_01_FromStart_a</column_1><column_2>怪我によって目覚め、難破した体が痛みに震える。敵はあなたが死んだと思って捨てて行ったようだが、それでもここでうかうかしてはいられない。力を振り絞り、死ぬ気で体を動かして入口へと向かうも、あなたは再び意識を失った。</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_01_FromStart_b</column_1><column_2>It is hours before you regain consciousness. You are beaten and bloody, but alive. You will wear these scars for quite some time...You curse your recklessness and vow to be more prepared for danger in the future.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_02_GEP_a</column_1><column_2>You fall to the ground, broken and defeated. As you start to black out from the pain, you sense someone standing above you, defending you! A warm voice reaches you through the haze of pain. "Whoa there, now! It ain't your time to die today. Stay with me, I'll look after you."</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_02_GEP_b</column_1><column_2>Stars and campfires dance in your fevered mind. Your eyes flutter open and you find yourself someplace safe. A warm campfire roars nearby, a note and mysterious bottle propped up beside it. You are alone, but you feel like someone was just here a moment ago...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_03_HyenasDefeat_Cherso_a</column_1><column_2>You raise you arms, shielding your vulnerable throat from the animals that howl at you, and brace yourself for death...Fangs sink into your leg and you feel yourself dragged across the ground. Every rock and bump causes jolts of pain that knock you into darkness for a while...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_03_HyenasDefeat_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>When you finally come to and open your eyes, you see the half-eaten leg of some poor explorer inches from your face. Hyenas howl nearby, hungry for flesh. Clearly, dinner has been served!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_04_BanditSouthCampPrisoner_Cherso_a</column_1><column_2>You wake from unconsciousness to see a bandit tying your hands together, and chaining you to a line of other prisoners. A lash from a whip stings your arm as you are ordered to run through the night. Your captors run you and the others ragged until their camp finally enters your vision...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_04_BanditSouthCampPrisoner_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>The miserable cries of your fellow prisoners fill the air as you are shoved into iron cages, and left to stew in total darkness. You get to work on forcing the bolts off the prison door. It’s hard work, but eventually you succeed. It’s time to make your escape!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_05_Immaculate_a</column_1><column_2>You fall to the ground, broken and defeated. As you start to black out from the pain, you sense something standing above you, defending you. A cold voice reaches you through the haze of pain. "Are you alive? Answer me!"</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_05_Immaculate_b</column_1><column_2>You awaken hours later, underground. As you lift up your head, a shape moves in the corner of your eyes. It is a monstrous beast that walks on two legs, red pulsing veins running along its body.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_05_Immaculate_c</column_1><column_2>The creature must have saved you! You see it holding a book in its hands, as it lets out a quiet laugh. Your consciousness fades again for a few minutes, before you manage to get up.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_06_Hermit_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>Hours later, you awake to find yourself in a small hovel with an old man smoking a pipe, who smirks at you. "You lack Reason. Be thankful for the Wind of Kindness, for it bore me to you in your time of need. Perhaps more care in the future will do you good, hmmm?"</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_07_CierzoInn_a</column_1><column_2>You can’t stand anymore, the very act of breathing is becoming difficult. Pain wracks your body as your consciousness fades…</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_07_CierzoInn_b</column_1><column_2>The warm smells of Cierzo's inn greet you. It seems someone found you on the edge of death and nursed you back to health. You have been out cold for days, though at the least you're still alive...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_08_CierzoDoors_b</column_1><column_2>You awaken to the sight of a huntress from Cierzo pouring water into your mouth. Leaning on her, you manage to hobble back to Cierzo, more dead than alive. She refuses payment and leaves you with a firm pat on the shoulder.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_09_BanditSouthCampTrashed_Cherso_a</column_1><column_2>You wake up to see a bandit tying your hands together, and chaining you to a line of other prisoners. A lash from a whip stings your back as you are ordered to run through the night. Your captors run you ragged until their camp finally enters your vision...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_09_BanditSouthCampTrashed_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>A wave of nausea from the death march you were forced to make rises from your stomach, and you vomit onto the cold hard ground, before falling into your own mess. By the time you get back up, you are alone. They seem to have no use for sick prisoners...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_10_BanditNorthCampPrisoner_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>You force your eyes open and find yourself in a cart with prisoners and corpses, bouncing along the road. A corpse hanging from a gibbet passes your vision...As unconsciousness takes you, you know that you have been taken prisoner by the Montcalm Tribe...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_10_BanditNorthCampPrisoner_Cherso_c</column_1><column_2>Hours later you open your eyes again, imprisoned within the Montcalm Village. You have no doubt they intend for your corpse to join the others dangling outside!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_12_CD2_Entrance_a</column_1><column_2>Pain wracks your body as you wake up from your injury. You are alone, but surely not safe. With clenched teeth, you manage to drag yourself outside to safety, where you fall unconscious again.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_19_BanditNorthCampTrashed_Cherso_c</column_1><column_2>You awake from the verge of death, corpses piled on top of you. With great effort, you pull yourself free, and find yourself outside rough wooden walls. The Montcalm tribe appear to have mistaken you for dead...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_20_VendavelPrisoner_a</column_1><column_2>Your eyes open to the sight of a Kazite woman pointing a sword right between your eyes. You are in no state to resist as she binds your hands and blindfolds you, and forces you to march. You hear bandit activity loud all around you.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_20_VendavelPrisoner_b</column_1><column_2>Your captor boots you into a cell and slams cold iron bars behind you. "Here's how it goes slave! Work when we tell you to, and you’ll get food and water. Or refuse to work, and it's to 'The Hole' with ye!"</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_21_TroglodytesDefeat_a</column_1><column_2>Without the strength to fight, you can only watch helplessly as Troglodytes surround you, chittering in their barbaric language, and haul you through their cave. The foul smell of rotting meat fills your nostrils as they dump you into a large, well lit room.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_21_TroglodytesDefeat_b</column_1><column_2>Troglodytes gather around a large stone pot over a fire, sometimes staring at you hungrily. Suddenly, a noise echoes in the cave and the monsters freeze. The dimwitted creatures then grab spears and charge out, leaving you alone.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_22_Watchers_a</column_1><column_2>Your body and mind are broken, all that's left is to await the release of death...Strange purple auras swirl around you and you give yourself to them, riding a strange dreamlike current, passing stars and ghostly figures...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_22_Watchers_b</column_1><column_2>It is the dull aches that wake you. The magical auras are not gone, but now you can sense their source. You are in the central chamber below the Conflux Mountain, in the care of the Watchers of the Ley Line...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_23_GhostPrisoner_a</column_1><column_2>Defenceless, you cannot stop the approach of the ghostly figure that bears down on you. It speaks to you in a language you cannot recognize, but the intention is clear - do not resist! It grabs your arm and drags you through the Ghost Pass, sword ready if you try to escape...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_23_GhostPrisoner_b</column_1><column_2>Your journey ends at a broken old cell whose door has long since fallen away. The ghost drops your arm, and turns away, motioning to slam the long-gone door into place and twisting a "key" into the air, before marching away.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_23_GhostPrisoner_c</column_1><column_2>The sign on the cell is in the Old Language, but it's easy enough to guess that it reads "marked for execution". You thank your lucky stars that the ghost was trapped in its old memories, unable to reason and think...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_25_CierzoHome_b</column_1><column_2>You awake to the familiar scent of your old home at the Lighthouse in Cierzo, warm and tucked into your bed, your backpack propped up beside you. Someone must have brought you back home and nursed you back to health. You’re not sure how long you’ve been unconscious...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_31_BergInn</column_1><column_2>When your eyes open, you find yourself wrapped up in a bed at the inn in Berg, having been unconscious for days. The innkeeper has helped himself to your Silver to pay for your stay, but you are otherwise alive and healthy.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_32_BergDoors</column_1><column_2>When you next awake, you are being carried by a hunter from Berg, on his way back to the city. He lets you down gently at the city gates with a gruff “Watch yourself out there, you were nearly a manticore’s dinner!”</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_39_LevantInn</column_1><column_2>You awaken wrapped in silk sheets at Levant’s inn, apparently having been nursed back to health after several days. The treatment and food has not come cheap either, judging by how light your coin pouch has become. Well, you live to fight another day!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_40_LevantDoors</column_1><column_2>It is pure luck that brings a mercenary company to your aid. To your relief, his band brings you back safely to the gates of Levant, free of charge. They then go off merrily to the inn, clearly going to brag to the serving girls about how they saved your life and didn’t even ask for payment...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_43_HMD2_Entrance</column_1><column_2>You wake up in the marsh. The Ash Giants, not knowing what to do with your unconscious body, dumped you outside their village. You can’t help but feel a little miffed at this rude treatment.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_49_MonsoonInn</column_1><column_2>The smell of sweet incense greets you as you awaken from the fevered dreams of the last few days. A passing missionary must have brought you to the Inn in Monsoon. The innkeeper has used money from your own pouch to pay for your treatment, but at least you’re still alive.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_50_MonsoonDoors</column_1><column_2>As your eyes open, you find yourself propped up against a wall at the gates of Monsoon, safe. As you glance around for your saviour, you see someone in gleaming white armor vanish into the crowd...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_51_CierzoHomeTuto</column_1><column_2>Unconsciousness comes quickly, and you dream of being ensnared in something. With a yelp, you jump out of your bed. Relief floods you as you recognize where you are. You are back in your old bed at home, the Lighthouse in Cierzo.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_51_CierzoHomeTuto_b</column_1><column_2>Yzan must have brought you back to your family’s lighthouse. Only your aching body tells you that the shipwreck you suffered was not a nightmare.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_52_Vigile</column_1><column_2>Visions of monsters fill your fevered dreams, and something stalks you relentlessly though twisted nightmares. You awaken, overwhelmed by a sense of paranoia and terror. You see one of the Vigil crystals up above... How in Elatt’s name did you end up here?</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_53_Watchers2</column_1><column_2>Purple grass surrounds you as you stir from unconsciousness high atop a mountain. Your life-threatening injuries have been bandaged by a hooded man, who silently turns to leave, entering a door along the mountain wall without a backwards glance...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_54_JustWakeUp</column_1><column_2>You hover in and out of consciousness for hours, until at last you are able to get back up. Nothing seems to have harmed you while you were out cold. You got lucky…</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_55_SavedByGhosts</column_1><column_2>You wake up to see a butterfly resting on your nose, someplace quiet. As you pull yourself up you notice a trio of ghosts guarding you...yet they soon vanish as if they were never there...It would seem that the Ancestral Memories sent you aid in your time of need.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_56_SavedByGiants</column_1><column_2>The smell of ash and cinder wakes you. The wide grin of a travelling Giant merchant greets you as you open your eyes. “Haloo, there, small human! That was a close call, no? You are lucky Silvernose came to your rescue!”</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_56_SavedByGiants_b</column_1><column_2>He pats a large backpack. “I have things in here for to prevent you from being in trouble again! My prices are very good, small human!” It would seem that your alliance with the Giants has just saved your life.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_57_RobbedByThugs</column_1><column_2>You snap awake with a yelp, feeling someone reaching into your various pouches. The hooded man pilfering your belongings jumps to his feet and sprints away at an impressive pace with his two companions.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_57_RobbedByThugs_b</column_1><column_2>A quick check confirms the worst. He’s helped himself to a lot of your valuables. You wonder how these criminals knew to find you out here...You sense that someone must have sent them after you, but who?</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_58_Elatt</column_1><column_2>As you see your life flash before your eyes, a brilliant light blinds you. As your eyes adjust once more, you find yourself laid on the ground someplace safe outdoors. Elatt’s intervention has no doubt saved your life.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_59_SteakosaursDefeat</column_1><column_2>Loud screeches startle you awake. You’ve been dragged into a cave, surrounded by the lizards of the marsh, screeching and fighting one another for the right to feast on you! You must flee, if you value your life!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_61_GiantsVillage</column_1><column_2>The first thing you notice, as you come to your senses, is that you are in a bed much too large for you. An Ash giant speaks in a rough, incomprehensible language as he tends to you. It would seem your alliance with them has saved your life.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_62_MonsoonHome</column_1><column_2>Dull aches wake you from your days-long comatose state. Your injuries and needs have been seen to, and you have been returned to your home in Monsoon. Whoever tended to you left no sign of their identity, nor have they taken payment.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_64_InsectsDefeat</column_1><column_2>The blood rushes to your head as you awaken upside down, cocooned by massive predatory bugs. With great difficulty, you free yourself and fall to the hive floor. If you do not intend to be dinner tonight, you should make yourself scarce from this place.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_65_CorsairsCampPrisoner_a</column_1><column_2>Desert bandits pounce on you and tie you up in a sack, before dragging you across the sand dunes. You pass out from the heat and lack of air more than once.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_65_CorsairsCampPrisoner_b</column_1><column_2>You wake up deep underground, at a bandit’s camp in an old crumbling mine. No doubt they intend to use you as slave labor. You cut the ropes that bind you on a nearby rock and prepare to make your escape!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_66_CorsairsHivePrison_b</column_1><column_2>Hours later you wake up and break free of the bag, only to find yourself in a prison cell surrounded by deadly insects. With great effort, you manage to force the bolts on the door off and stumble out of the cell. It’s time to beat a hasty retreat, before the insects grow hungry!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_67_LevantHome</column_1><column_2>You’re first aware that an army medic is pouring water into your mouth, then that you’re back at your manor in Levant. The medic declines payment, only saying “It’s been taken care of.” You’ve been out for days, but you’re still mostly in one piece.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_68_Slums</column_1><column_2>A dark, lonely alley greets you as you open your eyes. Someone from the slums of Levant must have found you and brought you to safety. A quick check confirms that they’ve helped themselves to your pouch of money as repayment while they were at it!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_69_VendavelTrashed</column_1><column_2>Your head aches, resting on rotten driftwood, your body submerged in water. A glance upwards shows only a small speck of light from the top of “The Hole”. You were exceptionally lucky to survive a fall like that.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_69_VendavelTrashed_b</column_1><column_2>With great effort, you swim in the murky water until you see a ray of light... You’ve escaped the Fortress of Vendavel, but paid dearly for it.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_71_BergHome</column_1><column_2>Days later, you return to your senses, neatly tucked into your bed at your home in Berg. It seems that someone brought you home, and Rissa or one of her attendants nursed you back to health from the brink of death.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_72_BurningMenDefeat</column_1><column_2>The smell of your own sizzling flesh wakes you, in agonizing pain. Burning Men walk nearby, almost oblivious to your presence. You don’t know why they’ve taken you prisoner, but given that they tried to set you on fire...You clearly don’t want to find out.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_73_HiveMenDefeat</column_1><column_2>Something bitter trickles from your mouth as you wake, cocooned by venomous insect creatures. As you free yourself, you can feel their poison coursing through your veins. You may not have much time left before the poison takes you...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_74_ThirstTuto</column_1><column_2>Your injured body can take no more, and you pass out from the continued trauma. When your eyes open once more, you are safe at a campsite along the beach. You vow to take better care of yourself in the future.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_301_BCQ1_DefeatByLevantAgents</column_1><column_2>Your head throbs as you pull yourself up. Gabriella Sullivan gives you a little patronizing wave from nearby. It would seem she saved your life from the criminals who have attacked the Blue Chamber.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_302_BCQ1_DefeatByLevantScouts</column_1><column_2>You come to, tied to a stake not far from the outpost, left for the beasts and Burning Men to finish off. Fortunately, they ignore you as you free yourself from the stake and arm yourself for another round!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_303_BCQ1_DefeatByLevantScoutsLeader</column_1><column_2>You brace yourself for the killing blow, but it does not come. You crack an eye open to see your foe fleeing at full speed. In your state, you will never catch up to him...It would seem that the one who led the assault on Berg has gotten away.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_304_BCQ2_DefeatByCyr</column_1><column_2>You wonder what you were thinking, as Cyr lifts you up with one hand. He makes a loud, rousing speech to his people in the giant’s tongue, then he walks right to the gates of his village and hurls you as far as he can. As you hit the ground, the doors slam shut for good.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_305_BCQ3_DefeatByRoland</column_1><column_2>As Roland’s possessed body approaches for the killing blow, you see him for a moment regain control and hold himself back. You take this as your cue to flee for your life to a safe part of the Necropolis to tend to your wounds.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_306_BCQ4_DefeatByBattleborn-01</column_1><column_2>You awaken in one of the beds in Berg's inn, suffering from a broken rib. The news you hear as you recover is grim indeed, Sagard Battleborn has gone rogue with a large battalion of the army. They will likely be a thorn in everyone’s side for a very long time to come.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_306_BCQ4_DefeatByBattleborn-02</column_1><column_2>Berg falls into a brief period of chaos without it’s Chamberlord, but by the time you can walk again, Gabriella Sullivan has been chosen to be Chamberlady. She seems none too pleased, but life in Berg will go on.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_307_BCQ4_DefeatByMonsoonHorrors</column_1><column_2>Cheers make you open your eyes through the haze of pain. It would seem the battle is over, and you’ve been dragged to the side with the other injured. While you’re disappointed you missed the end of the fight, as least you’re still alive to tell the tale.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_308_HMQ1_DefeatByGhosts</column_1><column_2>Screams rip from your throat as the corrupted ghosts plunder your life force greedily. Suddenly, a blast of light fills the room, and you see Oliele’s blade cut through your attackers. As you struggle to get up, you see that your friend’s ruined body has been forever changed...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_309_HMQ3_DefeatByRebelPriests</column_1><column_2>You feel Soeran patching up your injuries as you slowly regain consciousness. A quick glance around confirms that it was a massacre. Not a single one of the rebel priests is still alive. Oliele has completely vanished. Is seems she has forever abandoned the Holy Mission...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_310_HMQ4_DefeatByBattlebornThugs</column_1><column_2>You haul yourself to your feet, beaten and bloody. Those thugs from the Blue Chamber Collective beat you to within an inch of your life, then slaughtered the prisoners...Elatt will no doubt be upset.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_311_HMQ5_DefeatByImmaculate</column_1><column_2>As the Immaculates pounce on you without mercy, the ground beneath you crumbles, and you fall into darkness. By the time you pull yourself out, your foes seem to have regained their senses and fled the cave. They will no doubt be a danger to Monsoon in the future.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_312_LQ1_DefeatByLevantAgents</column_1><column_2>You cough up soot and ash as you wake up. The chamber is caked in dust, and a large hole yawns wide in the wall above you. The attackers seem to have detonated an explosive and left you to take the blame...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_313_LQ2_DefeatByBCScoots</column_1><column_2>You cough up sand as you stir from unconsciousness. You are beaten and bloody, but alive. It would seem that those Blue Chamber Scouts still uphold the tradition of not killing foes unless truly needed, or they mistook your for dead.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_314_LQ4_DefeatBySoldiers</column_1><column_2>You open your eyes in the abandoned docks, inches from death. You have no idea how long you’ve been out, but by now the coup against Levant is likely in full swing. You should hurry if you intend to stop them!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_315_LQ4_DefeatByCyrene</column_1><column_2>You open your eyes, and can tell by the stench that you’ve been thrown onto a pile of corpses. It seems Cyrene mistook you for dead.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_316_LQ5_DefeatDuringPrinceFight</column_1><column_2>The bustle of the Levantine Palace rouses you. From the chatter around you, you can guess that the raid against the Prince was successful, despite your injury. An aide informs you that the Queen wishes to reward your service. You should speak with her once you’ve recovered.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_318_HMQ1_DefeatByCorruption</column_1><column_2>Corrupted Ghosts surge from the Altar, their emergence blasting you away. Oliele drops to the floor, her veins turning a sick glowing green from the Corruption she absorbed. These twisted Ghosts crave your very life! You must defend yourself!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_3120_HMQ4_TrueDeath_01</column_1><column_2>We've all dreamed of being heroes, haven't we? Chosen by destiny, given sacred protection, unrivaled ability...</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_3120_HMQ4_TrueDeath_02</column_1><column_2>Divine heroes walk among us, and for a brief moment, you were one of them. You gave your mortal life so that another could live.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_3120_HMQ4_TrueDeath_03</column_1><column_2>Even now, as your vision dims forever, the impact of your deed remains a key part of the history of Aurai.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_3120_HMQ4_TrueDeath_04</column_1><column_2>Even now, as you feel yourself be pulled towards what lies beyond, to join your ancestors...You can't help but feel pride at what you accomplished.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Camping_NoEvent</column_1><column_2>Fortunately, your rest goes without incident and you feel better prepared for the day ahead.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Camping_Ambush</column_1><column_2>Your rest is interrupted by the faintest of unnatural sounds! You scramble to protect yourself from the ambush!</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Prologue_1</column_1><column_2>All my life, I've lived within the safety of Cierzo, spared the brutality of the world outside. But life in Aurai is never that easy. For all the safety that my tribe provides, our laws are harsh. We are judged not as individuals, but as bloodlines.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Prologue_2</column_1><column_2>The failures of my bloodline weigh heavy on me. My grandmother brought ruin to our tribe long ago, bringing a heavy Blood Price upon my family. We’ve paid the debt caused by her actions ever since.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Prologue_3</column_1><column_2>I joined an expedition across the sea with my old friend Yzan, hoping the money made there would be enough to clear my debts. This was a mistake. I’m lucky to still be breathing after our ship hit rocks on the return voyage.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Prologue_4</column_1><column_2>Now, I have no choice but to pick myself up yet again and face the wild, untamed land outside the walls. I must carve out my own future, or die trying.</column_2><column_3></column_3><column_4></column_4><column_5></column_5><column_6></column_6></ooo_row>
  </ooo_sheet>
</ooo_calc_export>
